<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scalars on TravelgateX Documentation</title>
    <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scalars on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/travelgatex/reference/scalars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boolean</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/boolean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/boolean/</guid>
      <description>The Boolean scalar type represents true or false.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Boolean   Required by AccessData:    SupplierData:    Provider:  Temporary type to use only during SQL server&amp;#39;s lifetime  PageInfo:    SupplierFilter:    ClientFilter:    ClientData:    OrganizationData:    GroupCommonData:    GroupData:    Member:  You grant access to members which can be either: Users: A developer, administrator or any other person from your Organization who interacts with the TravelgateX Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CVC</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/cvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/cvc/</guid>
      <description>GraphQL schema definition scalar CVC   Required by PaymentCard:  Input PaymentCard, if the payment is done by credit card, is it mandatory to specify the payment type and the credit card information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CardNumber</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/cardnumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/cardnumber/</guid>
      <description>GraphQL schema definition scalar CardNumber   Required by PaymentCard:  Input PaymentCard, if the payment is done by credit card, is it mandatory to specify the payment type and the credit card information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Country</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/country/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/country/</guid>
      <description>The Country type represents Country values. A good example might be a Passenger Nationality. In queries or mutations, Country fields have to be specified in ISO 3166-1 alpha-2 format with enclosing double quotes &amp;ldquo;ES&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Country   Required by Location:  Indicates the location of the hotel  HotelCriteriaSearchInput:  Search criteria contains destination, travel dates and the number of pax in each room. You must preload the other fields in our system by complete the fields absents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currency</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/currency/</guid>
      <description>The Currenty type represents Currency values. A good example might be a Rate Price Currency. In queries or mutations, Currency fields have to be specified in ISO 4217 format with enclosing double quotes &amp;ldquo;EUR&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Currency   Required by HotelCriteriaSearchInput:  Search criteria contains destination, travel dates and the number of pax in each room. You must preload the other fields in our system by complete the fields absents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Date</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/date/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/date/</guid>
      <description>The Date type represents Date values. A good example might be a Hotel CheckIn Date. In queries or mutations, DateTime fields have to be specified in ISO 8601 format with enclosing double quotes: &amp;ldquo;2017-10-22&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Date   Required by HotelCriteriaSearchInput:  Search criteria contains destination, travel dates and the number of pax in each room. You must preload the other fields in our system by complete the fields absents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DateTime</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/datetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/datetime/</guid>
      <description>The DateTime type represents DateTime values. A good example might be a transaction TimeSpan. In queries or mutations, DateTime fields have to be specified in ISO 8601 format with enclosing double quotes: &amp;ldquo;2017-10-22T13:57:31.123Z&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar DateTime   Required by Access:  An Access is a set of credentials and configuration in order to access the system of a Supplier.  Node:    Supplier:  A Supplier is a Partner who is connected to TravelgateX on the supply side in order to sell their product to connected Buyers  Client:  Client identifies who is making the request and holds the configuration assigned to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Float</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/float/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/float/</guid>
      <description>The Float scalar type represents signed double-precision fractional values as specified by IEEE 754.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Float   Required by Coordinates:  Geographical coordinates corresponding to a location.  Stat:    AuditData:  Data sent and received in the supplier’s native format.  Price:  Price indicates the value of the room/option. Supplements and/or surcharges can be included into the price, and will be verified with nodes Supplements/Surcharges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ID</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/id/</guid>
      <description>The ID scalar type represents a unique identifier, often used to refetch an object or as key for a cache. The ID type appears in a JSON response as a String; however, it is not intended to be human-readable. When expected as an input type, any string (such as &amp;quot;4&amp;quot;) or integer (such as 4) input value will be accepted as an ID.
GraphQL schema definition scalar ID   Required by AccessFilter:    Access:  An Access is a set of credentials and configuration in order to access the system of a Supplier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Int</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/int/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/int/</guid>
      <description>The Int scalar type represents non-fractional signed whole numeric values. Int can represent values between -(2^31) and 2^31 - 1.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Int   Required by SupplierData:    SupplierFilter:    ServiceOperation:  Information related to an API operation  GroupData:    RelayInput:    HotelXHotelListInput:    HotelXRoomQueryInput:    HotelXDestinationListInput:    HotelXDestinationSearcherInput:    PaxInput:  Pax object that contains the pax age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/json/</guid>
      <description> The JSON type makes sure that it is actually valid JSON and returns the value as a parsed JSON object/array instead of a string. In queries or mutations, JSON fields have to be specified with enclosing double quotes. Special characters have to be escaped: &amp;ldquo;{\&amp;ldquo;int\&amp;rdquo;: 1, \&amp;ldquo;string\&amp;rdquo;: \&amp;ldquo;value\&amp;ldquo;}&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar JSON   Required by AddOns:  Additional information about the option  AddOn:  Additional information about the option   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JWT</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/jwt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/jwt/</guid>
      <description> JSON Web Tokens are an open, industry standard RFC 7519 method for representing claims securely between two parties.
GraphQL schema definition scalar JWT   Required by AdminQuery:  The admin query root of TravelgateX&amp;#39;s GraphQL interface.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/language/</guid>
      <description>The Language type represents Language values. A good example might be a Hotel Description Language. In queries or mutations, Language fields have to be specified in ISO 3166-1 alpha-2 format with enclosing double quotes &amp;ldquo;es&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar Language   Required by Text:    HotelCriteriaSearchInput:  Search criteria contains destination, travel dates and the number of pax in each room. You must preload the other fields in our system by complete the fields absents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>String</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/string/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/string/</guid>
      <description>The String scalar type represents textual data, represented as UTF-8 character sequences. The String type is most often used by GraphQL to represent free-form human-readable text.
GraphQL schema definition scalar String   Required by AccessEdge:    AccessData:    SupplierData:    Provider:  Temporary type to use only during SQL server&amp;#39;s lifetime  Error:  Application errors  Parameter:  Parameters for additional information for the supplier&amp;#39;s configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>URI</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/uri/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/uri/</guid>
      <description> The URI type represents a URI values. A good example mith be an Hotel Image URL. In queries or mutations, URI fields have to be specified in RFC 3986, RFC 3987, and RFC 6570 (level 4) compliant URI string format with enclosing double quotes: &amp;ldquo;http:\www.travelgatex.com&amp;rdquo;.
GraphQL schema definition scalar URI   Required by Urls:  Url&amp;#39;s  Contact:  Contact Data.  Media:  Contains media information.  UrlsInput:  URLs Input  StatsAssert:  Assert of an specific error   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>examples__JSON</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/examples__json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/reference/scalars/examples__json/</guid>
      <description> GraphQL schema definition scalar examples__JSON   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>