<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deprecated Notes on TravelgateX Documentation</title>
    <link>/tags/deprecated-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deprecated Notes on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/deprecated-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deprecated Schema Notes</title>
      <link>/hotelx/release-notes/deprecated_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hotelx/release-notes/deprecated_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes that can break existing queries to the GraphQL API. For example, removing a field would be a breaking change Under construction! We have logged this resource on our roadmap and we are currently working through extending all of the resources in our documentation. If you need specific resources (such as this page), please let us know by using one of the following channels:
 Join us on Slack and let us know what resources you need us to prirotize Send us a Jira service desk request Log an issues request with us Write this page yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deprecated Schema Notes</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/deprecated_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/release-notes/deprecated_notes/</guid>
      <description>Changes that can break existing queries to the GraphQL API. For example, removing a field would be a breaking change    Deprecation date Deletion date Days left Name Location Deprecation Reason     2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed hotel Booking You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed booking Query You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed hotel Quote You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed hotel Search You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed createDefaultSettings Mutation You can find it in query at Admin   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed loadFile Mutation You can find it in query at Admin   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed search Query You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed quote Query You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed deleteDefaultSettings Mutation You can find it in query at Admin   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed defaultSettings Query You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed mapping Query You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed hotelBook Mutation You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed hotelCancel Mutation You can find it in query at HotelX   2017-11-21 2018-02-19 Already passed updateDefaultSettings Mutation You can find it in query at Admin   2017-12-12 2018-03-12 Already passed useContext HotelSettingsInput Redundant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>