<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on TravelgateX Documentation</title>
    <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on TravelgateX Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/travelgatex/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/release-notes/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>We have put together a GitHub Project where we will keep updating on the things we’ve in our plans.
Here is the GitHub project with Public Roadmap of TravelgateX.
The Project has a few columns that act as the status whereas cards are the items that we have in our plans. We have also labelled each issue so it would clarify if the item would be added in the HotelX, Documentation, etc&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/release-notes/changelog/</guid>
      <description>To make it easier for users and contributors to see precisely what notable changes have been made on TravelgateX.
All notable changes on TravelgateX platform will be documented in this page.2018-08-08  GraphQL Schema updated.    TGX Headers page Support basic Tracing by request using header TGX-Tracing: 1 Return groups codes in entities queries (accessData,suppierData,clientData,profileData).   2018-07-31  GraphQL Schema updated.    Fix IAM mutations    Delete member mutation (Delete Apikeys or uninvite user emails)   2018-07-30  Improvements on the organization selector  Sorted organizations by alphabetical order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL Schema Changes</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/graphql-schema-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/release-notes/graphql-schema-changes/</guid>
      <description>The GraphQL schema change log is a list of recent and upcoming changes to our GraphQL API schema. It includes backwards-compatible changes, schema previews, and upcoming breaking changes.
Check out this list of new releases and changes applied on the TravelgateX GraphQL API.
2018-08-08 ✅ Input field currency was added to input object type SettingsBaseInput
✅ Field parents was added to object type GroupData
✅ Deprecation reason on field Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GraphQL Schema breaking changes</title>
      <link>/travelgatex/release-notes/breaking-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travelgatex/release-notes/breaking-changes/</guid>
      <description>Changes history of deprecated notes previously announcedUnreleased  Removal of organization from PaymentXBookingInfoFilterInput. Reason: Please use PaymentXBookingInfoCriteriaInput. Deprecated on 2018-08-03.Expected removal on 2018-11-01. Removal of pointOfSaleCode from PaymentXBookingInfoFilterInput. Reason: Please use PaymentXBookingInfoCriteriaInput. Deprecated on 2018-08-03.Expected removal on 2018-11-01. Removal of bookingReference from PaymentXBookingInfoFilterInput. Reason: Please use PaymentXBookingInfoCriteriaInput. Deprecated on 2018-08-03.Expected removal on 2018-11-01. Removal of error from Group. Reason: Sustituted by adviseMessage. Deprecated on 2018-08-01.Expected removal on 2018-10-30. Removal of distribute from AddOns.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>